<resources>

    <string name="app_name">MAKS 2013</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>

    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>Plan of the complex</item>
        <item>List of participants</item>
        <item>Business Program</item>
        <item>Flight program</item>
        <item>About programm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="name">name:</string>
    <string name="note">description:</string>
    <string name="p">Pavilion:</string>
    <string name="z">Hall:</string>
    <string name="dp">Business program events at International Aviation and Space Salon MAKS 2013 will be held on 26-30 August. The events will be attended by executive officers and experts from the largest Russian enterprises and foreign companies, prominent scientists and representatives of top ranked technical higher educational establishments and universities.\n
\n
Highest public officials, heads of federal and regional executive agencies and organizations, individuals representing military-political leadership and broad spectrum of business structures have been invited to attend the events.\n
\n
Tight Business program will offer Russian and foreign participants a unique opportunity to actively share professional knowledge and information on advanced practices and know-how, global technology and business solutions in aircraft industry; the program contributes to creating conditions that will encourage Russian business community to focus attention on Russian state-of-the-art engineering developments and promotes Russian aviation industry achievements.\n
\n
The events important for current and future situation in the industry as a whole have been included into Business program which will be held in a format of special topic conferences, sessions and round table events attended by Russian and foreign experts. Business program covers all the range of topics associated with aircraft industry development, encompassing vital issues that deal with development of favorable investment climate in the industry.\n
\n
MAKS 2013 Business Program Includes:\n
\n
International Aviation Congress. Organized by: The Ministry of Industry and Trade of the Russian Federation, Aviasalon JSC, Directorate of International Air Transport Forum (IATF) in Ulyanovsk.\n
Scheduled dates: 27-28 August 2013.\n
\t <a href="http://www.aviasalon.com/_files/upload/maks_2013/delovaya_programma/program_of_%20congress_en.pdf">International Aviation Congress Program (~ 130 KB)</a>\n
\n
Sixth European Air Cargo Transport Congress.\n
Organized by: German-Russian Economic Alliance, Aviasalon JSC.\n
Scheduled date: 26 August 2013.\n
\t  <a href="http://www.aviasalon.com/_files/upload/maks_2013/delovaya_programma/program_of_air_cargo_transport_congress.pdf"> Program of the Sixth European Air Cargo Transport Congress (~ 730 KB)</a>\n
\n
Details on the web-site: www.deruwia.de\n
\n
Session of Business Council of Interstate Commission on Military and Economic Cooperation of the Collective Security Treaty Organization (CSTO).\n
Organized by: CSTO Secretariat.\n
Scheduled date: 28 August 2013.\n
\n
International Scientific and Practical Conference:\n
Composite Materials in Civil and Military Aircraft Industry.\n
Organized by: Union of Composites Manufacturers.\n
Scheduled date: 30 August 2013.\n
<a href="http://www.aviasalon.com/_files/upload/maks_2013/delovaya_programma/events_of_the_business_program_22.08.pdf"> Events of the business program MAKS-2013 (~570 KB)</a>\n
<a href="http://www.aviasalon.com/_files/upload/maks_2013/delovaya_programma/terms_of_participation_en.pdf"> Terms of participation in the business program (~ 210 KB)</a>\n
</string>
<string name="lp_label">Visit to official web site</string>
<string name="about">About programm</string>
<string name="admob_publisher_id"></string>
<string name="about_text">This is unofficial application for MAKS-2013 for navigation. \n\nDeveloper: <a href="mailto:mksmbtrsh@gmail.com">Maksim Bartosh</a> (<a href="https://play.google.com/store/search?q=maksim+bartosh&amp;c=apps">my apps in GooglePlay</a>)\n\nThis programm used GPLver2\n<a href="https://github.com/mksmbrtsh/maks2013/">source code on github.com</a></string>
</resources>